# Luiz Bossetto

🗣 Bloomington, Illinois 🔀 luiz.fbossetto@outlook.com 📞 (309) 856-0506 🛮 in Luiz Bossetto 🔘 luizfboss

# **PROFILE**

A passionate, self-driven, and creative Computer Science student. Possess excellent technological expertise, welldeveloped communication skills, and the essential ability to perform well in a team. Aim to expand my knowledge, learn from experienced team members, and help others through what technology can offer.

# **EDUCATION**

Illinois Wesleyan University

Bloomington, IL

Pursuing a Bachelor of Arts - August 2022, Present

- Major: Computer Science
- Minor: Data Science
- GPA: 3.82

Colegio Singular

Santo André, Brazil

High School - January 2019, December 2021

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

**CSS** Microsoft Excel Adobe Illustrator HTML + Bootstrap **JavaScript** Python SQL +ReactJS C++

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

01/2022 - 05/2022 Web Designer Freelancer Brazil

Developed websites for local businesses, increasing brand exposure and improving

revenue.

**Coding Mentor** 08/2021 - 09/2021

Grow&Share Brazil

In charge of teaching coding skills to high school students whose school does not offer Coding classes.

Student Manager

09/2022 - Present Sodexo - Illinois Wesleyan University Bloomington, Illinois

Prepare and cook food ensuring the highest quality service and experience for customers

(students and faculty).

## **LANGUAGES**

English Portuguese Fluent. TOEFL Certification Native Speaker

## **COURSES**

Web Development - Mastering Web Development 01/2022 - Present

Faus

Introduction to ReactJS 07/2022 - 08/2022

FreeCodeCamp

Introduction to JavaScript 08/2021 - 10/2021

Google & Curso Em Video

Python - From Basic to Advanced 01/2021 - 11/2021

Geek University

Motion Design and Game Development 08/2018 - 01/2021

School of Art, Games, and Animation